（探照灯影业）
♪ Tonight you're mine completely ♪
♪ 今晚你属于我 ♪
♪ You give your love so sweetly ♪
♪ 你把爱给得温柔如蜜 ♪
♪ Tonight the light of love is in your eyes ♪
♪ 今夜你眼里有爱的光辉 ♪
♪ Will you still love me tomorrow? ♪
♪ 但明天你还会爱我吗？ ♪
One minute...
请稍等...
Get somebody down there
快派个人去那里
Ma'am, are you okay?
女士 您还好吗？
Can you hear me?
您能听见我说话吗？
I got someone on the south lawn,
南草坪上有人受伤
we need paramedics over here right away
我们需要急救人员立刻过来
Copy that.
收到
Jesus Christ, what happened to you?
天呐 你这是怎么了？
- In-laws. - Did you say in-laws?
- 婆家 - 你说是婆家吗？
What about your in-laws, ma'am?
你的婆家怎么了？女士
Hey, hey, hey, stay with us.
嘿 嘿 嘿 别昏过去
Just keep your eyes on me.
睁眼看着我
Take it easy.
放松
Slow, steady breaths.
慢慢呼吸
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
哇 哇 哇
She's down!
她倒下了
Get that stretcher over here!
把担架抬过来
Get her loaded up. On my count, one hand down.
先把她抬上去 数到三一起抬
Critical condition.
情况危急
Ready?
准备好了吗？
One, two, three!
一 二 三
One, two... Up!
一 二 抬
Stay with us.
挺住
She in?
她还活着么？
Yeah.
是
Let's get a set of vitals on her.
给她测一下生命体征
I'm gonna get oxygen on.
我这就给她接氧气
Mask's on.
氧气面罩已戴好
I'm gonna check pupils.
我要检查一下瞳孔
Orthostatic.
体位性低血压
I don't have a pressure.
血压测不出
No pupil response.
瞳孔无反应
Let's check her pulse.
检测脉搏
No pulse.
无脉博
She's in cardiac arrest.
她发生了心脏骤停
Starting compressions.
开始胸外按压
Charging.
充电中
Two hundred.
200焦耳
Ready.
准备
Clear.
清场
Ortho coming in with a Caucasian female.
正在运送一名体位性低血压的白人女性
Mid to late twenties.
年龄在二十五岁左右
In severe shock.
处于严重休克状态
Multiple lacerations.
多处撕裂伤
Possible gunshot wound through the left hand.
左手中可能有枪伤
Through and through.
子弹贯穿
Pulse.
脉搏？
No pulse.
无脉博
I'll get her compressions again.
我这就继续做胸外按压
Charging.
充电中
Two hundred.
200焦耳
Clear.
清场
- Hide and seek？ - She's here!
- 捉迷藏？ - 逮到她了
I'll test you.
我来帮你检测
Three, two, one.
三 二 一
You'll see.
你会明白的
《准备好了没2：我来了》
字幕贡献者
pubuqi（SubHD）
Borcolasky（SubHD）
小p（蒙太奇字幕组）
Mrs. Le Domas?
勒多马斯太太？
Where am I?
我在哪里？
You're in Woodbury, Connecticut.
您现在位于康涅狄格州的伍德伯里
St. John's Hospital.
圣约翰医院
Why am I handcuffed?
为什么给我戴手铐
- Mrs. Le Domas. - It's Ms. MacCaullay.
- 勒多马斯夫人 - 叫我麦考利小姐
It says here you married an Alex Le Domas.
这里写着您嫁给了亚历克斯·勒多马斯
It didn't work out.
那段婚姻没能维持下去
I'm Detective Roger Bassett.
我是罗杰·巴塞特警探
You're in some trouble, Ms. MacCaullay.
你有麻烦了 麦考利女士
You're being detained by the Woodbury Police Department.
你现已被伍德伯里警察局拘留
Under suspicion of arson and murder.
涉嫌纵火和谋杀
They found the remains of two people in the house
扑灭大火后 他们在屋内发现了
after they put out the fire.
两具遗体
And your clothes were drenched in blood.
你的衣服上沾满了鲜血
It wasn't yours.
并且那不是你的血
Now, if you'd care to make a statement.
如果你愿意做个陈述
Could you pass me a cigarette?
能给我支烟吗
This is not going to go well for you, Ms. MacCaullay.
麦考利女士 这对你可没什么好处
Things would go a lot easier if you would just cooperate.
只要你配合 事情会好办很多
She has a visitor.
有人来看她
Are you expecting someone?
你在等人吗？
Oh, shit.
哦 天呐
Look at you.
看看你
What are you doing here?
你来这里干什么？
Well, I'm still your emergency contact.
嗯 我还是你的紧急联系人
So, thanks for that.
谢了
Who are you?
你是谁？
Faith MacCaullay.
费丝·麦考利
Who are you?
你又是谁？
Family?
一家人？
Biologically speaking, yeah, we're sisters,
生物学意义上 对 我们是姐妹
but we're not family.
但我们不是一家人
Okay.
好吧
I'm going to give you a few minutes.
我会给你们几分钟时间
Then I'm going to take you to the station.
然后我会带你去警局
Get that statement.
做陈述
What happened?
发生什么事了？
You wouldn't believe me.
你不会信的
That's probably true, but I drove all
这话可能没错 但我大老远开车
the way out to bumfuck Connecticut,
来到康涅狄格这个鬼地方
- so... - Where'd you come from?
- 所以... - 你从哪儿来的？
You mean, where do I live?
你的意思是我住在哪里吗？
Sure.
是的
Murray Hill.
默里山
I'm in Chelsea.
我现在在切尔西
Yeah, cool.
酷
How long have you lived in New York?
你在纽约住了多久了
I moved out there when I was 18.
我十八岁时搬过去的
Just like you.
就像你一样
- And you never thought... - Grace, come on.
- 你竟然从没想过... - 格蕾丝 得了吧
You made it very clear a long time ago that
很久以前你就说得很清楚了
you're not interested in being my sister, okay?
你不想做我的姐姐 好吗？
And the feeling's mutual.
我也是这么想的
I'm not here for a reunion.
我来这里不是为了重聚
Yeah, it's good to see you, too.
好 见到你我也很高兴
How are you?
你好吗？
- I'm fucking amazing. - Yeah?
- 我他妈好极了 - 是吗？
Yeah, really good.
真好极了
I'm a social media coordinator.
我现在做自媒体
I live in a kick-ass one bedroom and
我住在一间超棒的一居室里
I have a hot-as-fuck boyfriend named Derek.
还有个帅得要命的男朋友 叫德里克
And I didn't have to fuck Alex Le Domas to get it.
而且我不用靠跟你的亚历克斯·勒多马斯上床来得到这些
I did it all by myself.
全靠我自己的努力
How do you know about Alex?
你怎么知道亚历克斯
I saw you together once at
有一次我在第七大道二十五街的
the Whole Foods on 25th and 7th.
全食超市看到你们在一起
He's tall.
他很高
You could have said something.
你本可以打个招呼的
Why?
为什么？
I'm in a good place.
我活的那么好
You're a negative person.
干嘛去见你这个唠叨鬼
I'm not a negative person.
我才不是唠叨鬼
- And even though you abandoned me... - I did not abandon you.
- 尽管你抛弃了我 - 我没有抛弃你
I still believe in the fundamental goodness of humanity.
我依然相信人性的善良
Oh my God, if you knew what I'd just been through...
天呐 如果你知道我刚才经历了什么...
Then tell me.
那就告诉我吧
I told you you wouldn't believe me.
我说过 你不会相信的
Alright, I'm glad you're okay.
好 你没事就好
But you haven't changed.
还是这个苦瓜脸
I'm just gonna go.
那我走
Faith, wait.
费丝 等一下
After the wedding, Alex tells me I have to pull a card.
婚礼结束后 亚历克斯告诉我 我得抽一张牌
Play whatever game it says.
玩上面写的任何游戏
Some kind of
某种...
initiation ritual.
入会仪式
Which I thought was weird.
我起初觉得挺奇怪
But I wanted them to like me
但我想让他们喜欢我
because they were gonna be my new family.
毕竟他们要成为我的新家人了
Anyway...
总之
I pull hide and seek.
我抽到了捉迷藏
And it gets real quiet.
然后 周围人立马安静了
Because apparently...
显然
That's the bad card.
那是一张坏牌
And they think they have to try to sacrifice me to the devil.
他们以为必须把我献祭给魔鬼
They told me I could win.
他们告诉我 有机会赢
If I stayed hidden till dawn.
如果我能躲到天亮
But they thought...
但他们认为
If I won...
如果我赢的话
They'd die.
他们会死
So they hunted me.
然后他们开始猎杀我
I got...
我
Shot through the hand.
手中枪了
Beat to shit by a butler.
被一个管家打得半死
And my...
并且我的
My husband... Stabbed me.
我的丈夫 刺伤了我
But I made it till dawn.
但是我撑到了天亮
I fucking won.
我他妈赢了
So...
所以
Did they drop dead?
他们死了吗？
No.
不
They blew up.
他们爆炸了
爆炸了？
And then after they blew up, there was a guy in a chair.
在他们爆炸后 有个男人坐在椅子上
And he nodded at me.
他朝我点了点头
Who was the guy in the chair?
椅子上的男人是谁？
I don't know.
我不知道
But he was see-through, so I'm pretty sure he was...
虽然他是透明的 但我非常确定他是...
You know...
你懂的...
You are so going to jail.
你肯定要进监狱了
Yeah.
是的
（战事陷入胶着 结束遥遥无期）
Approve the ceasefire.
批准停火
（突发新闻 双方同意停火）
Good morning, Mr. Danforth.
早上好 丹福斯先生
It's been a long time.
好久不见
I have some news.
我有些消息
Leave us.
出去
The Le Domases are no more.
勒多马斯家族没了
Pernilla.
佩妮拉
Can you find my children?
你能把我的孩子叫来吗？
Of course.
当然
I'll inform the others.
我转告其他人
（今晚有好戏了）
（新娘活下来了 勒多马斯家族失败了 游戏继续）
Hello.
喂
Get all my lawyers here right now.
马上把我的律师都叫来
Right away.
马上
（进击工作室）
The collection of the weathered houses.
历经岁月沧桑的古老宅邸合集
Clothurnburg. Charlotte.
克洛特恩堡 夏洛特
¡Deja el puto pelo, Carmen!
（西班牙语）别弄他妈的头发了 卡门
¡Coño!
（西班牙语）操
Who wrote this shit?
这破玩意谁写的
I'll just wing it.
我就即兴发挥吧
I'll do my own thing.
我按自己的方式来
Like always.
像往常一样
¡Puta madre!
（西班牙语）真见鬼
¡Me cago en esta puta!
（西班牙语）真是他妈的大好事
¡Ven ya, Katia!
（西班牙语）过来 卡蒂亚
¡Ay, Dios!
（西班牙语）哦 天呐
Hey, all right.
嘿 好了
Tell William the guy shot the jet.
告诉威廉 那人搞砸了
（鲜肉公司）
It's my time, motherfucker.
轮到我了 混蛋
Benson.
本森
Bring me my knife!
把我的刀给我
This is our chance!
这是我们的机会
Le Bail be praised!
勒拜尔万岁
Yeah!
耶
Shot!
开干
（丹福斯）
Father
父亲
So the Le Domas failed.
所以勒多马斯家族失败了
The bride survived.
新娘活下来了
The ball is in play.
游戏继续
No.
不
That's not fair.
那不公平
It's... it's ours!
这是我们的
It doesn't matter.
没关系
It's in the rules.
规则就是这样
You know what you have to do.
你们知道该做什么了吧
Dad.
爸
Please.
求你了
Be a fucking man!
像个爷们
You're a Danforth.
别忘了你姓丹福斯
This... must never leave our family.
这绝不能离开我们家族
You must win the seat back.
你必须夺回这个席位
We will.
我们会的
You have my word.
我保证
Well...
好吧...
Get on with it.
痛快点吧
Titus.
泰特斯
It's over.
结束了
Not for the bride.
对新娘来说还没结束
All right, Mrs. MacCaullay.
好了 麦考利夫人
We'll get you some clothes.
我们给你拿些衣服
Then continue our conversation at the station.
然后我们到警局继续谈话
I can't wait for you to tell me about that goat...
我迫不及待想听你讲那只山羊的事
It's all gonna be yours.
这一切都会是你的
Fuck the rules!
去他妈的规则
Please, please.
求你了 求您了
Mrs. Le Domas!
勒多马斯夫人
What is going on
这他妈什么情况
This can't be happening again
这事怎么又开始了
Listen, I need a weapon.
听着 我得有武器
I'm going back to the car.
我先回车里拿
Do not leave me
别抛弃我
Okay, Okay
好的 好的
You hurting me!
你伤到我了
Not so good at hide and seek now!
你现在的捉迷藏水平也不咋样嘛
Oh my God! What the fuck!
哦天呐 搞毛线啊
Okay.
好了
There could be more coming.
可能还有更多的人来
I gotta get out of these cuffs.
我得把手铐弄开
Okay?
还好吗？
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼
We gotta get out of here and disappear.
我们得赶紧走
What the fuck are you doing?
你他妈在干什么？
We might have to fight.
我们可能需要打架
I can't fight in this gown.
穿着病号服我没法打架
No time to look for new clothes.
没时间找新衣服了
You have to fight?
你还要打架？
Okay, okay.
好的 好的
Come on, we gotta go.
快点 我们得走了
What a mess.
真是个乱摊子
Looks like Mr. Wilkinson tried to.
威尔金森先生显然想
Killed the girl before the game could begin.
在游戏开始前就杀了女孩
And condemned his entire bloodline to a premature end.
并让他的整个血脉过早地走向灭亡
Well, that's what happens when you break one of Mr. LaBelle's rules.
嗯 这就是违反拉贝尔先生规则的下场
Hello there.
你好
And who might you be?
请问你是谁？
And right then I knew that we were both going to make it.
就在那一刻 我知道我们俩都会挺过去的
Because we had this moment to live for.
因为我们有这一刻值得为之而活
And here we are.
而如今 我们就在这里
We made it.
我们做到了
I love you so much.
我爱你
Mark.
马克
When we met that day in the chemo ward.
那天我们在化疗病房相遇
Ladies and gentlemen.
女士们先生们
I am terribly sorry to tell you but I'm going
我非常抱歉地告诉你们
to have to ask you all to vacate the premises.
我不得不请你们所有人离开这里
Unfortunately, we have a gas leak.
不幸的是 我们出现了煤气泄漏
Are you fucking kidding me?
你他妈在开玩笑吗？
She's not.
她没有
Kindly get the fuck out.
请你赶紧滚出去
Besides, you could do way better.
此外请你礼貌点
Attention ladies and gentlemen.
各位请注意
do on procedures...
请根据指示...
These people need to go home.
这些人该回家了
Get the fuck out.
滚出去
Why do you always feel the need to be such a dick?
你为什么总觉得非得当个混蛋不可？
Your little grace goes a long way.
你但凡有点善意都意义非凡
Well, that was funny.
好吧 那很可笑
Today is not the day for funny.
今天不是搞笑的日子
Dad gave us a mission and I'm not going to let him down.
爸爸给我们一个任务 我不会让他失望
Yo!
呦
Cousins!
表亲们
How long has it been?
已经过去多久了？
I'm gonna sign it up.
我先报个名
Come get me when the fireworks start.
好戏开场时来叫我
Dick tap!
摸你鸡鸡
You don't have to speak to him.
你不必跟他说话
Just don't start anything, okay?
别惹事 行吗？
Not today.
今天别惹事
Fucking Kip.
该死的基普
It had to be done.
我们非做不可
You look just like him when you're sad.
你伤心的时候看起来真像他
I'll repeat, please remain calm and proceed to the exits in an orderly fashion.
我再说一遍 请保持冷静 有序地走向出口
Ladies and gentlemen, pack up your shit and get the fuck out.
女士们先生们 收拾好你们的破烂 滚出去
Please.
请快点
When was the last time the council actually convened in person?
委员会上次举行现场会议是什么时候？
October, 1963.
1963年10月
I looked it up.
我查过了
Well, they're on their way to the lodge now.
嗯 他们现在正前往小屋的路上
And so it begins.
开始了
Oh, man.
哦 天呐
Yeah.
是啊
Ignacio.
伊格纳西奥
Felipe.
费利佩
Buenos Días, Senora Danforth.
早上好 丹福斯夫人
You haven't aged a day.
你一点没老
No Francesca?
弗朗西丝卡没来吗？
I thought for sure she'd want to be here for this.
我原本以为她肯定想亲眼见证这一刻
She'll be along, believe me.
她马上就来 相信我
She wouldn't miss this for the world.
她不会错过这个的
It's exciting...
真是件好事
it's exciting for me.
嗯 对我来说真是件好事
It's terrifying for you.
对你来说不是
Yes, and you.
对 还有你
Vamos, Felipe.
走吧 费利佩
Ursula.
乌苏拉
Titus.
泰特斯
You remember my son? Cheng Fu
你还记得我儿子吗？承福
I know you, Chengfu. Welcome.
认识你承福 欢迎
What's the Wi-Fi password?
Wi-Fi密码是什么？
Be nice
态度好点儿
Madhu
马杜
Viraj
维拉杰
Martina, welcome.
玛蒂娜 欢迎
So how's this shit work?
规则是什么？
Our guests will be arriving soon, and then the lawyer will explain everything.
大家马上到齐了 到时候律师会向大家说明一切
Ah, lawyer.
啊 大律师
Speak slow for this beautiful dum-dum over here.
跟这边这位漂亮笨蛋说话慢点
Single-syllable words.
爆破音
It appears our guest of honor is arriving.
看来我们的贵宾要到了
Hello, Grace.
你好 格蕾丝
I'm Ursula Danforth.
我是乌苏拉·丹福斯
This is my brother Titus.
这是我哥哥泰特斯
Welcome to our home.
欢迎来到我们家
May I speak to her, Father?
父亲 我可以跟她说话吗
Sí, sí, ándale, Felipe.
（西班牙语）可以 可以 去吧 费利佩
It can't hurt you.
它伤不着你
Did you see Mr. LeBail?
你见到勒贝尔先生了吗？
One second.
等一下
I just gotta take a quick selfie before we start.
在开始之前 我得先拍张自拍
Yo!
呦
This girl bested the Le Domases.
这女孩打败了勒多马斯家族
And Bill Wilkinson.
还有比尔·威尔金森
Can we start this, please?
我们能开始了吗？
And where the fuck is Chester?
切斯特他妈在哪儿？
Our father... passed.
我们的父亲...去世了
What the fuck?
搞什么
What?
什么？
Last night, in his sleep.
昨晚 在睡梦中
Wait, wait, wait.
等等 等等
So does that mean that you're playing now?
那意味着你现在要参赛了
As we are twins, we will both be taking the field, yes?
既然我们是双胞胎 那我们俩都会上场 对吧？
What the fuck?
搞什么鬼？
No.
不
How convenient.
多方便啊
Te dije que los Danforths son unas víboras.
（西班牙语）我早就跟你说过 丹福斯一家都是阴险小人
Está bien.
（西班牙语）没事的
Y que iban a hacer trampas.
（西班牙语）他们在耍诡计
Ya, no te preocupes
（西班牙语）行了 别担心
Grace, I realize this must be terrifying for you.
格蕾丝 我明白这对你来说一定很可怕
But you are here for a very special,
但你来到这里 是因为一个非常特别
very exciting reason.
非常令人兴奋的原因
You've caused quite a stir, Mrs. Le Domas.
勒多马斯夫人 您可真是掀起了不小的风波
MacCaullay!
我叫麦考利
I am the sole attorney for Mr. LaBelle and the LaBelle organization.
我是拉贝尔先生和拉贝尔组织的唯一律师
The organization is led by a council made up of the heads of six families,
该组织由一个理事会领导 该理事会由六个家族的首领组成
including your in-laws.
包括你的婆家
Now The DeMoss and Wilkinson families have been wiped out.
现在德莫斯和威尔金森家族已经被消灭
The council of six families is currently down to four.
六大家族议会目前缩减到四个
The reason you're here is
你在这里的原因是
that by surviving Le DeMoss' game of hide and seek,
你从勒德莫斯家的捉迷藏游戏中幸存下来
you triggered a very seldom use
你触发了我们组织章程中一条
clause in our organization's bylaws.
极少被援引的条款
You see, on the council there is
要知道 在理事会中
one seat with more power than the others.
有一个席位的权力比其他席位更大
The high seat.
至高席位
And it comes with this, sigil of power.
它配有这个权力徽章
Until now, that seat was occupied by Chester Danforth.
直到现在 那个席位由切斯特·丹福斯占据
I presume you've heard of him.
我想你听说过他
Because you triggered that clause, the high seat is
因为你触发了那个条款 至高席位现在空缺了
now vacant for the first time in many, many years.
很多很多年来的第一次
And, believe it or not,
而且 信不信由你
you've been given an opportunity to win the high seat.
你获得了一个赢得至高席位的机会
It's very rare that someone survives a game,
能从游戏中幸存下来的人非常少
so it comes with this reward.
所以会获得这份奖励
And the heads of the remaining council families
其余议会家族的首领们
will try to win the seat for themselves.
也会竭力争夺这个席位
Or in our case, take back what should still be ours.
或者就我们而言 夺回本应属于我们的东西
This clause is so fucking stupid.
这个条款真他妈蠢
Ah, you're afraid one of us is going to take Daddy's place, eh?
啊 你是怕我们其中一个会取代你爸爸的位置 是吗？
You never know.
谁知道呢
Mrs. Le DeMoss could win.
勒德莫斯夫人可能会赢
So, as Ms. Danforth said, this is all actually good news.
因此 正如丹福斯女士所说 这其实全是好消息
Mr. LeBail has smiled upon thee.
勒贝尔先生向你展示了笑颜
Hail Satan.
赞美撒旦
Do you...
你
have any questions?
你有什么问题吗？
I have
我有
Can I have a cigarette?
能给我一支烟吗？
No.
不
Your sister's existence was quite a surprise.
你妹妹的出现真是个意外
You told the Le Domas that you had no family, and yet, here is faith.
你告诉勒多马斯家族你没有家人 然而 费丝在这里
Grace and faith, fucking Irish Catholics.
格蕾丝和费丝 他妈的爱尔兰天主教名字
【译注: 格蕾丝英语意为赞美 费丝意为信念】
Listen.
听着
We can make this real quick,
咱们赶紧结束吧
because I don't want your fucking chair.
因为我他妈的才不要你的席位
I suppose I wasn't clear.
我想我没有说清楚
The high seat controls the council, and the council controls...
至高席位控制议会 议会控制着
well, everything.
嗯 一切
Everything?
一切？
The world.
整个世界
So what, I just have to pull another card or something?
那又怎样 我就得再抽一张牌之类的吗？
That won't be necessary.
没有那个必要
Think of this as double or nothing.
把它想成双倍或全输的赌局吧
Because you survived Le Domas' game of
因为你从勒多马斯家族的捉迷藏游戏中
hide and seek, you will play that game again.
幸存下来 你将再次玩那个游戏
No!
才不要
This time, with the council members.
这次 是和议会成员一起
Fucking baby shit bun.
他妈的小屁孩
So for me to win the seat?
所以 我怎么赢？
Survive until dawn.
活到天亮
And the rest of them?
其他人呢？
This part will be familiar.
这部分你很熟悉
They will try to kill you.
他们将会杀死你
Whoever does, wins the seat.
谁杀了你 赢得至高位
Now, we must fill the seat by dawn,
现在 我们必须在天亮前填补这个空缺
or Mr. LeBail will be...
否则勒贝尔先生就会...
very upset.
非常不高兴
- The winner will... - Ah! Fuck yeah!
- 获胜者将... - 太棒了
You silly.
臭孩子
Hail Satan.
赞美撒旦
The winner will be coronated in
获胜者将在黑神庙
a special ceremony in the Black Temple.
举行的特别仪式上加冕
The crème de la crème of Mr. LeBail's
勒贝尔先生最虔诚的信徒们
faithful will be in attendance.
将悉数到场
That's the whole thing.
就这些
I'm not playing.
我不玩
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦 对不起
That's the other thing.
还有一件事
I'M NOT PLAYING!
我不玩
You have to compete.
你必须参赛
I'm still not playing.
我还是不玩
Okay.
好吧
Prunella, kill the sister.
普鲁内拉 杀了那个妹妹
NO! NO! NO!
不 不 不
FUCK!
操你妈的
DON'T HURT HER!
别伤害她
You can take that off.
你可以把这个拿掉
Listen!
听着
You guys seem like good people!
你们看起来都是好人
And I don't even know why I'm here!
而且我甚至都不知道自己为什么会在这里
We haven't seen each other in, like, seven years!
我们大概有七年没见过了
Why not?
为什么不见面？
It's complicated.
这很复杂
Nice leverage, moron.
好手段啊 蠢货
This thing doesn't even care about the other thing.
她根本不在乎那个女的
You two don't get along?
你们两个合不来？
We had a falling out.
我们闹翻了
About what?
因为什么？
Just her being an asshole.
就因为她是个混蛋
Look, allow me to wrap up.
听着 让我总结一下
The game will begin at exactly 2:31 p.m.
游戏将在下午2点31分准时开始
In observance of the exact time Mr.LaBelle...
为遵守拉贝尔先生所指定的确切时间...
Daddy!
爸爸
Mi amor.
（西班牙语）我的宝贝
Well, holy shit, here you are.
嗯 天呐 你来了
Okay.
好吧
Francesca El Caído, you dumb slut.
弗朗西丝卡·埃尔卡多 你个蠢荡妇
Okay.
好吧
Alex's ex-fiancee.
亚历克斯的前未婚妻
Where the fuck is my ring, bitch?
我的戒指他妈在哪 婊子？
He bought it for me before you stole him.
在你偷走他之前 他买给我的
I threw it at him right before he exploded.
就在他爆炸之前 我把它扔向了他
You're nothing but a cold-hearted whore.
你不过是个冷血的婊子
You see, Alex wasn't stupid, but he sure was fucking gullible.
要知道 亚历克斯并不傻 但他确实他妈的太好骗了
You ruined my life.
你毁了我的生活
And I don't even know who the fuck you are.
而我他妈都不知道你是谁
Okay, No, no, no.
别生气 别生气
Ladies and gentlemen, we should get moving.
女士们先生们 我们应该行动了
Pernilla.
佩妮拉
Wait.
等等
I want to do it.
我想动手
No, no, no.
不 不 不
I want to...
我想
I just want you to know it's going to be me who gets you.
我只是想让你知道 会是我抓住你
- Okay? - No, no, no.
- 懂吗？ - 不 不 不
No!
不
No, no, no, I just an Emergency Contact!
不 不 不 我只是紧急联系人
The council members must use a weapon that existed
理事会成员必须使用一种
during the period in which their ancestor...
在其祖先与勒贝尔先生达成协议的时期内
..made his or her bargain with Mr.LeBail.
就已存在的武器
The council members are not allowed to kill each other.
议会成员不得互相残杀
If they do, even by accident, Mr. LeBail will be angry.
如果他们这样做了 即使是意外 勒贝尔先生也会生气
And the offending family's entire bloodline will be punished.
而那家有罪之人的整个家族都将受到惩罚
Beyond that, anything goes.
除此之外 百无禁忌
I... I don't want to use the blood pen.
我不想用血笔
Or can you at least sterilize it.
你至少可以把它消毒一下吧
Fuck's sake.
该死
The families may observe the proceedings from the club room.
家族成员可以从俱乐部房间观察过程
In the unlikely event that any of the hunters should perish,
万一有猎人不幸身亡
the next person in that family's line
该家族继承序列中的下一位成员
of succession must take their place on the field.
必须立即接替其位置 投入战斗
Best of luck to you all.
祝你们好运
Aren't you going to change, bro?
你不换衣服吗 兄弟？
Why?
为什么？
None of us are going to have to go out there.
我们谁都不需要出去
Chester trained his kids since they could walk
切斯特从孩子们刚会走路起就开始训练他们
in case this day ever came.
以防这一天真的到来
This will be over in five minutes.
五分钟内就会结束
There.
那里
It better be.
最好是这样
I got a massage in an hour.
我一小时后有个按摩
The girl will begin the game on the ninth hole green.
这位女孩将从第九洞果岭开始比赛
Hunters, take your places.
猎手们 就位
The game will begin in ten,
游戏马上开始 十
nine, eight, seven,
九 八 七
six, five, four,
六 五 四
three, two, one.
三 二 一
There are no fucking keys.
没钥匙怎么开
Oh, did I forget to put the keys in there?
哦 我是不是忘记给你们钥匙了？
Fuck. Cheaters!
操 你作弊
Go!
开车
- Idiots - Spoof you, Suckers.
- 白痴 - 这群傻瓜
Faith
费丝
Yeah
嗯
Faith, wake up!
费丝 快起来
Please, stop it.
求你了 停下
Come on.
快起来
We gotta get up. We gotta move.
我们得起来 我们得赶紧走
Shit!
妈的
We gotta get up.
我们得起来
Shit!
操
Fuck!
Oh, God!
我了个天呐
They're coming!
他们来了
Why do they want to hurt me?
为什么他们想伤害我？
They don't give a shit about you.
他们根本不在乎你
You're here to slow me down.
你在这儿只会拖我后腿
If you don't do exactly what I say, we are going to die.
如果你不按照我说的做 我们将会死
Do you understand?
你明白了吗？
So we obviously share the seat when we get it back,
所以我们夺回那个席位后 显然得共享
but who gets to wear the ring?
但戒指该谁戴？
Well, Dad wanted me to be the one in charge, so...
嗯 爸爸希望由我来负责 所以...
Bullshit.
放屁
He told me.
他和我说过
Well, he told me.
嗯 他告诉我
It should be me.
我来戴戒指
No, he didn't.
不 他没有说过
We're gonna get to the woods.
我们需要去树林里
We're gonna go to the woods.
Wait, wait, wait.
等等 等等
What if there's people waiting for us in the fucking woods?
如果有人在树林里等着我们怎么办？
Stop.
停下
It's not a debate.
这没什么好争论的
I am in charge.
我说的算
Oh, you're in charge?
哦 你说的算？
It's your fucking fault I'm here.
我之所以在这里 全都是你他妈的错
All I did was forget to remove you as my emergency contact.
我只是忘了把你从我的紧急联系人名单里移除
It's been seven years.
七年了
You don't know anybody else.
你不认识其他人吗？
Fine.
好吧
Whoever kills her gets to wear the ring.
谁杀了她 谁就能戴戒指
I'm not agreeing to that.
我不同意
What the fuck is that?
那他妈是什么
God!
我去
Oh, shit.
哦 妈的
What is that?
那是什么
Whoa, hold on.
哇 等等
Listen. This is Wan Chenxing.
听着 我是万晨星
We met earlier.
我们之前见过
Whoa, hold on.
哇 等等
There's a way out of this.
有一个脱离这一切的方法
I had my lawyers scour the bylaws and we found a loophole.
我让律师仔细查阅了章程 结果发现了一个漏洞
All we have to do is...
我们所要做的就是...
Oh, my God!
哦 天呐
Nice shot.
打得好
There she is.
她在那
Get her.
抓住她
Oh, my God.
哦 天呐
God damn it.
该死的
Skippy, screens.
斯基皮 打开屏幕
They weren't supposed to make it off the green.
他们本不该离开果岭的
Give me the fucking thing.
把那破玩意儿给我
God damn it.
该死的
There's no way we're getting over that.
我们没有办法过去
There's gotta be a tree we could climb.
应该会有树可以爬的
Oh, we're gonna climb with handcuffs?
哦 我们带着手铐爬树
Okay.
好吧
Okay, okay, fuck.
好吧 好吧 操
Okay, turn it on.
好吧 打开它
What the fuck is this?
这他妈是什么？
No, just press input one.
不 只需按输入1
Yeah, no, it's right.
对 不 没错
Show me fucking input one.
告诉我那个该死的输入1
Go, press menu, and then go.
点击“开始” 然后点击“菜单” 再点击
My, you're stupid fucking idiots.
你们他妈真是蠢透了
Where the fuck are they?
她们再他妈哪儿？
Grace, we've been running forever!
格蕾丝 我们跑了好久了
Fuck, ow, fuck!
操 嗷 操
Can you just slow down, please?
你能慢点嘛？
Oh, I'm sorry.
哦 对不起
Okay.
好吧
I can't believe you dragged me into this shit.
我不敢相信你把我卷入到这破事中
How does this even happen?
这是怎么发生的？
You're telling me you didn't know your fiancé was in a devil cult?
你是说你不知道你老公信邪教？
Seems kind of hard to miss.
这似乎很难不注意到
I mean, your attention must have been on all that money.
我猜你大概只顾着数钱了
What?
什么？
What does that mean?
你什么意思？
Nothing, I'm just saying that I work for my shit,
没什么 我只是说我的钱都是自己挣的
and I don't need some rich dick to solve my problems.
我不需要靠有钱人来解决我的问题
Fuck you.
去你的
- Fuck you. - Fuck you.
- 去你的 - 去你的
Okay, what does Derek do?
好吧 德里克是做什么的
Finance.
金融
Oh, and I'm chasing Rich Dick?
哦 那是我在追有钱人？
He was a starving actor when we first met.
我们刚认识的时候 他还是个穷演员
Starving actor with a fallback MBA?
饿肚子的演员 还有金融硕士学位？
You think I made up Derek?
你以为我是编造了德里克这个人的吗？
Kinda now, yeah.
现在有点 对
You think I'm pathetic.
你觉得我可悲
You just can't handle it that I made it and you didn't.
你就是见不得我混出头 而你没有
Grace?
格蕾丝
There's no use in hiding.
躲起来没用
I know you think we're the bad guys here.
我知道你觉得我们是坏人
But there are no good guys or bad guys.
但是没有好人坏人
There's just the system.
只是体制就是这样的
Whether you realize it or not...
不知你是否意识到了
you're a part of it, too.
你也是这个体制的一部分
You contribute to it.
你也是其中的一分子
How you enable it.
你在助长它
I'm no more evil than you are.
我并不比你们更邪恶
We just a small part of something that is much bigger than us.
我们不过是某个远比我们宏大的东西的一颗螺丝钉
We can do it, we can do it, we can do it, we can do it.
我们能行 我们能行 我们能行 我们能行
And die with a little dignity.
带着点尊严去死
Handcuffs!
手铐
Go, go, go! Run, run, run!
快跑
Get up.
起来
Oh my God.
你真行
You cannot fuck up like that.
你可别搞砸了
The only way to make what we did to dad mean
要让我们对爸爸所做的一切有意义
something is to win that fucking seat back.
唯一的办法就是把那个该死的席位夺回来
Titus!
泰特斯
Do you understand?
你明白吗？
That is the only way it matters.
这是唯一的方式
Let's go to that building and look for a phone.
让我们去那座楼找个电话
The longer we're on this property, the better there are chances of finding us.
我们在这待得越久 被发现的可能性就越大
We need to figure out a way to get out of here.
我们要找方法离开这
Over that wall.
翻过那个墙
Let's just make a run for it.
我们直接冲过去
It's completely exposed.
那会完全暴露
You are too impulsive.
你太鲁莽了
You never think things through.
你从不考虑周全
Look, they don't have anywhere to hide either.
你看 他们也没地方躲
You're gonna get us both killed.
你会害死我们俩的
Y ahora me toca, toca a mí.
（西班牙语）现在轮到我了
A los Danforth ya los jodí.
（西班牙语）丹福斯一家被我搞定了
¿Qué vas a ganar, tía?
（西班牙语）你觉得你能赢吗？妹子
¡Ni eso ni pollos en vinagre!
（西班牙语）想的美
Joder, gilipollas.
（西班牙语）操白痴
It's too risky.
这太冒险了
Just, okay, just let me think this through.
行 好吧 让我先好好想想
Sometimes you gotta take a risk.
有时候 你得冒一次险
Is that gunfire?
那是枪声吗？
Por fin, ya, ya, ya, por fin
（西班牙语）终于 终于 终于
Oh, found him.
哦 找到他了
Who's fucking shooting them?
谁他妈在射她们
Your dad fucking sucks.
你爸真他妈是个废物
Shit.
他妈的
He never practices.
他从不练习
If she gets away, I swear to fucking God.
别让她跑了
（她们在第三洞的球道上）
Are you sure you want to do that?
你确定你要这么干吗？
I was just...
我只是
Oh Fuck!
操
He's getting better.
他射的越来越准了
No more fucking risk!
别他妈的冒险了
I have an idea.
我有个主意
¡Joder!
（西班牙语）操
Ahora que sí que me toca a mí
（西班牙语）现在轮到我了
¿Qué diablos es?
（西班牙语）搞什么鬼？
¡Mierda, mierda, mierda!
（西班牙语）妈的 妈的 妈的
¡Coño!
（西班牙语）操
Oh my God!
哦我的天呐
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go!
走 走 走 走
Fucker!
混蛋
Oh my God!
哦我的天呐
Don't look at it, don't look at it!
别看 别看
No, no, no, no, no.
不 不 不 不 不
¡De esta libré
（西班牙语）命真硬啊
Okay？
你还好吗？
Okay
好吧
¡Hijo de la gran puta!
（西班牙语）狗娘养的
Fuck!
操
Okay.
好
Okay. We've got to find a phone.
好 我们找到个电话
You're leaving a trail of blood behind.
血都流下来了
We need to sit down.
我们需要坐下来
Come on.
快点
Sit here.
坐在这
Sit.
坐下
Fuck.
操
Oh.
哦
Alright, let's do the little one.
好的 先从小的拔
One.
一
Two.
二
Three.
三
Just focus on me.
看着我
Ready?
准备好了吗？
Okay, what are you, a part-time nurse too?
好家伙 你现在还兼职当护士？
I don't know, maybe I am.
或许是吧
So, what did you do after you graduated?
你毕业后干什么了
Oh.
哦
I, um, I didn't finish.
我 呃...我没读完
I had to drop out.
我不得不退学
Seriously?
真的？
Yeah, then I waited tables.
是啊 然后我去端盘子
After all that follow your dreams shit?
说了那么多“追随梦想”的大道理 结果就是这？
Yeah, well sometimes dreams don't work out.
是啊 有时候梦想就是实现不了
And then I met Alex.
然后我遇到了亚历克斯
And that dream didn't work out either.
那个梦想也没实现
Okay.
好吧
It's gonna burn.
会有点疼
All right.
好了
I tried to find you, you know.
你知道吗 我找过你
I wanted to invite you to a wedding.
我想邀请你参加婚礼
I wouldn't have come.
我不会来的
I know, but I wanted you to know
我知道你不会来 但我想让你知道
that I wanted you there.
我是真心想邀请你的
Well, there's no fucking way you would have got me
嗯 你绝对没法让我穿上那些
in one of those ugly-ass bridesmaids' dresses, so...
丑得要死的伴娘裙 所以
Alright, alright.
好了 好了
Shot for the pain?
喝点？
Yeah.
耶
Although nothing's gonna numb the pain of being with you.
虽然没什么能减轻跟你在一起的痛苦
To surviving till dawn.
为了活到黎明
Again.
再一次
Come on, this way!
快点 这边
Okay, we're gonna need...
听着 我们...
we're gonna have to fight him. we can take it.
我们得跟他正面硬刚 我们能对付他
Fight him?
打他吗？
We gonna do.
我们必须这么做
It's okay. We can take it.
好吧 我们能行的
We've always had each other's backs in the fight.
打架的时候 我们一直是彼此的后盾
Okay?
好吗？
We can do this.
我们能做到的
That's gonna make a lot of waves.
声音太大了
We don't have choice.
没机会了
You hold still.
别乱动
你才别动
You can't hide!
你们无处可藏了
Fuck!
操
Oh my God, if it was me out there, she'd be dead.
老天 要是换我上 她早就死透了
Yes, of course, it'd be you.
是啊 当然是你了
Come on, come on, come on.
快点 快点 快点
Go!
走
Get that bitch!
抓住那个婊子
You!
你
We are gonna need some glasses, cause we're about to have a toast.
我们需要一些酒杯 因为我们要干杯了
Ha ha ha ha ha!
哈 哈 哈 哈 哈
- No. - No, no, no, no!
- 别跑 - 不 不 不 不 不
What the fuck?
这他妈是什么？
Bath time!
沐浴时间
（高温蒸洗）
No, no, hey, hey, hey!
哦 不 嘿 嘿 嘿
Ah!
啊
What are you doing?
你要干什么？
He might have a phone.
他可能会有手机
Jesus!
天呐
Fuck!
操
Oh god!
我的天
Shit!
妈的
Okay, Okay, God.
好吧 好吧 天呐
Can you help me, please?
你能帮我吗 求你了
No, you got this.
不 你自己可以的
You're doing great.
你做的很好
I'm not.
我就不行
I'll just get in the way.
我只会碍事
Oh, look!
哦 看
You did it!
你做到了
Thanks for your help.
我谢谢你啊
He's gone.
他死了
I'm so sorry for your loss.
对你的损失我很抱歉
Mr. Rajan?
拉詹先生
He's gone.
他死了
Mr. Rajan, as your brother has left this mortal plane,
拉詹先生 令兄既已仙逝
you may take the field.
您可以上场了
Do I have to?
我必须上场吗？
Your family must be represented by the eldest member
在所有继承审判中 您的家庭必须由最年长的成员
or legally appointed head of household in all trials of succession.
或依法指定的家主代表
Per Article 2, Section 3, Subsection C.
根据第2条第3款C项
Failure to do so would mean forfeiture of Mr. LeBail's favor.
若不从 则意味着失去勒贝尔先生的庇护
- You mean, um... - I'm afraid so.
- 你是说... - 恐怕是的
What about my wife?
我的老婆怎么样？
Are you saying you want to abdicate your status as head of the Rajan family?
你是要放弃拉詹家族族长的身份吗？
And make my wife hunt?
并且让我老婆狩猎
Yes.
是的
Jebem ti mater da ti jebem.
（克罗地亚语）操你妈的
I u pičku maternu i u sto pičke materne.
（克罗地亚语）操你祖宗十八代
Gade jedan gade!
（克罗地亚语）你个畜生
Crko da bog da!
（克罗地亚语）咒你不得好死
Motherfucker!
混蛋
I'll just need you to sign that.
请您在上面签个名
Madhu, if you sign that...
马杜 如果你签那个
I will make you very dead.
我会让你死得很惨
This is hard for me too.
我也不想这样做
Fuck it.
不管了
Okey dokey.
好吧 没问题
Ma'am, if you please.
请吧 女士
Okey dokey.
好的 没问题
911, what's your emergency?
911 你有什么紧急情况
I need help, my sister and I are being...
我需要帮助 我和我姐姐正在被...
We're at the Danforth Casino,
我们现在在丹福斯赌场
golf course, whatever, compound.
高尔夫球场 或者说那个综合设施里
People are trying to kill us.
有人要杀我们
I'm sorry ma'am, could you slow down and repeat yourself?
抱歉女士 您能说慢点 并重复一下吗？
I decided to capture all the outgoing calls on the compound
我决定监控大院内所有外拨电话
just in case they managed to get their hands on a phone.
以防他们设法弄到电话
How?
怎么做的？
We own the phone company.
我们拥有这家电话公司
And they're all devil worshippers.
而且他们全都是崇拜魔鬼的人
I know it sounds insane, but we need help.
我知道听起来很荒唐 但我们真的需要帮助
We're at the Danforth Resort, please send someone.
我们现在在丹福斯度假村 请派人过来
Yes, I understand.
好的 我知道了
We will send help right away.
我们会立即派人过去帮忙
Can you make it to the main gate?
你能赶到正门吗？
Yeah, we'll be there.
好的 我们会过去的
Ok.
好的
Are you sure about this?
你相信吗？
Yeah, I'm sure.
是的 我确信
I'm not here to hurt you.
我不会伤害你的
Do you hear that Faith?
你听到了吗 费丝
The lady with the sword isn't here to hurt us.
那个拿剑的女人不是来伤害我们的
Right.
对的
I have no desire to get into some punchy, kicky situation with you.
我可不想跟你打打杀杀
There's a way out of this.
有办法解决这个问题
I'm not here to kill you.
我不是来杀你的
I'm here...
我来这
to offer you a deal.
提出个交易
Alright, what is it?
好吧 怎么说
I had my lawyers scour the bylaws.
我让我的律师仔细查阅了章程
I don't think the other council members know this,
我认为其他成员不知道这个
but if you marry into a high council family,
如果你嫁给一个议会成员
if you marry my son, we get the seat and you get to live.
如果你嫁给我儿子 我们得到席位 而你也能活下去
Bullshit!
胡说
I swear to Mr. LaBelle.
我向拉贝尔先生发誓
She says yes.
她同意
No more Hunt.
不会再狩猎了
And look, I know your first marriage didn't end well.
听着 我知道你第一段婚姻结局不太好
But my Cheng-Fu isn't like Alex.
但我儿子承福不像亚历克斯
He's an idiot, but he's kind.
虽然他是个傻子 但是他很善良
And the world will be far better off without the Danforths pulling the strings.
如果丹福斯家族不再在幕后操控 世界会好得多
Grace.
格蕾丝
Titus is a psychopath.
泰特斯是个变态疯子
His sister won't be able to control him.
他姐姐控制不了他
And the world will go to hell faster than it already is.
世界会比现在更快走向末日
But you're a good person.
但你是个好人
Of course not.
当然不是
But it's a matter of degrees.
但这只是程度上的差别罢了
Right, okay, so I'm just married to some stranger.
好吧 那我就这么嫁给了一个陌生人
- Yes, but... - Great!
- 对 但是 - 太好了
You don't have to live as a couple.
你们不必像夫妻一样生活
You can do whatever you want.
你可以做任何你想做的事
Yeah, she'll do it.
对 她会做的
No.
不
What?
什么？
No, this seems too easy.
不...这也太容易了吧
What, I wouldn't have to do anything?
我什么都不用做吗？
Well...
好吧...
Okay, well, what would she have to do?
好吧 她必须做什么
Technically, she'd be part of the organization, but
严格来说 她算是组织的一员
she'd just have to do the usual stuff we all have to do.
但她只需要做我们大家都要做的那些常规工作
- It's not so bad. - What's that?
- 不算太糟 - 那是什么？
What's the usual stuff?
那些常规工作？
- I mean... - You mean sacrificing goats and shit and pigs?
- 我是说... - 你是说要献祭山羊 猪之类的？
Fucking killing innocent people?
他妈的杀害无辜的人？
Selling my fucking soul?
出卖他妈的我的灵魂？
Yeah, that's gonna be a no.
嗯 那还是算了
Puta madre.
（西班牙语）他妈的
Fuck off, Ignacio!
滚开 伊格纳西奥
You fucking weirdo!
你这个该死的怪胎
You know you can't kill me!
你知道你不能杀我
Say yes!
说同意
Right now!
现在
Move!
让开
If you don't, I have to kill you before he does!
如果你不说 我会在他动手之前杀了你
Jesus Christ!
天呐
I'll do it!
我同意了
I'll marry your fucking son!
我会嫁给你那该死的儿子
Chen! Hurry up! Move!
晨 快点 让开
Say yes, Jesus!
说 同意 天呐
Just say yes!
就说 同意
Just do it!
快说
Yeah!
该死
Please!
求你了
Chen!
晨
She'll do it!
她会同意的
She'll marry your fucking son!
她会嫁给你那该死的儿子
She has to say it!
她必须说
You have to say it!
你必须说
God damn it!
该死的
Why is everyone looking at me?
为什么大家都看着我
Okay, well...
好吧...
I'll need a fresh one of these, stat.
我得赶紧弄个新的来
And, uh, give me a poncho or something.
还有 呃 给我件雨披之类的
Thanks, Jen.
谢谢 珍
Yeah.
对
Okay.
好的
I'm really not used to people combusting all over me.
我真的不习惯有人在我面前自爆
Yeah.
对
No.
不
It's always surprising.
确实总是让人猝不及防
Why did you say no?
你为什么拒绝了
You could have saved us.
你本可以救我们
Uh, because I don't want to spend the rest of my life fucking killing people.
因为我不想后半辈子都他妈地去杀人
Okay.
好吧
That lady sold her soul.
那个女人出卖了自己的灵魂
I'm not gonna sell mine.
我不会做同样的事
I'd rather be dead than live like that.
我宁可去死 也不要那样活着
You wanna know why I don't take risks?
你想知道为什么我不想冒险吗
It's because the one time... I did.
因为我冒了一次险
I got fucked and moved to New York and I...
我去了纽约 结果被耍了 然后
and I lost you.
我失去了你
You didn't move to New York.
你没有搬去纽约
You left me.
你抛弃了我
Faith, we can't do this right now.
费丝 现在不是提这事的时候
You could have taken me with you.
你本应该可以带我一起走的
I was 18!
我当时18岁
It was a once-iN - a-lifetime scholarship.
那是一次千载难逢的奖学金机会
- How do you not... - We were a team.
- 你怎么会... - 我们是一个团队
You could have become my legal guardian.
你本可以成为我的法定监护人
You were 15?
你当时15岁？
I couldn't take care of you?
我怎么照顾你？
I could have helped with rent.
我可以帮助付房租
How?
怎么帮
It was New York.
那里是纽约
You were a kid.
你是一个孩子
Yeah, your kid sister.
对 你的孩子妹妹
I told you.
我告诉过你
I had a plan.
我曾有个计划
I was gonna make a better life for both of us.
我会为我们两个打拼出更好的生活
I was gonna bring you out once I graduated.
等我毕业了就把你接过来
Do you know how long three years is at that age?
你知道那个年纪 三年有多漫长吗？
Faith, you were okay.
费丝 你当时还好
You were safe.
你很安全
Grace... We had decent foster parents.
格蕾丝...我们的养父母人不坏
You had a roof over your head.
你有个栖身之所
Grace...
格蕾丝
You left me.
你抛弃了我
I called you for years.
我给你打了好几年电话
You didn't wanna talk to me!
你根本不接
I was mad.
我那时很生气
It broke my fucking heart.
你伤透了我的心
After you broke mine.
在你伤透我的心之后
You remember the last thing you said to me?
你还记得你对我说的最后一句话吗
I said, please don't go, and you said...
我说 求你了 不要走 你说...
"I have to.
“我必须走”
"There's no other way."
“没有其他选择”
I'm fucking sorry.
我他妈真的很抱歉
I'm happy for you.
我为你感到开心
I'm very happy for you and your perfect life.
我为你和你完美的生活感到开心
I made up Derek.
德里克这个人是我编的
I live in Bushwick,
我住在布什维克
and I'm not a social media manager.
也不是什么自媒体人
What do you do?
你干什么的
I'm a hostess.
我是个迎宾员
Technically, as a waitress, I outrank you.
严格来说 我是服务员 职级比你高
They made me a hostess because they said I'm so pretty.
他们说我太好看了 所以让我当迎宾
Yeah, but you don't get any tips.
是啊 但你拿不到小费
I get a lot of tips because I'm really pretty.
我收到很多小费 因为我真的很漂亮
Well, I don't need tips because my fake boyfriend Derek makes bank, so...
哈 我不需要小费 因为我那个假男朋友德里克赚大钱
Right, right, right, right.
对 对 对 对
God bless Derek.
上帝保佑德里克
Let's go.
我们走吧
Where are they?
他们在哪儿？
Shit, can you get that?
妈的 你能接那个电话吗
It could be them.
可能是她们
- Answer it. - I don't want to answer it.
- 接 - 我不想接
They can't get the same 911 operator twice.
她们不能两次找到同一个911接线员
The fuck do I say?
我他妈说什么
Just fucking answer it.
赶紧他妈的接就是了
911.
What's your emergency?
你有什么紧急情况
We're here.
我们到了
Where are the cops?
警察在哪儿？
Where are you?
你们在哪儿？
We're following a wall to the main gate.
我们沿着墙走向正门
I don't see a cop car.
我没看到警车
The unit is close.
警察在附近
Just wait there at the gate, and they will see you.
待在大门附近 他们会看见你的
You bitch.
你个婊子
Did you see that?
料到了吗？
Nice.
漂亮
So, we knew it was your voice on the phone, fucking dumbass.
所以 我们一听就知道是你的声音 他妈的蠢货
Yeah, idiots.
对 白痴
We've been watching you.
我们一直在监视你
Good for you.
你真行
All right, well, tell us how to open the gate.
好吧 嗯 告诉我们怎么开门
Well, you can only do that from the control room.
你只能在控制室操作
How do we get there?
我们如何到那
Yeah.
对
Well, you go back inside, you make a left.
嗯 你回去 左转
The elevator on the far right is the only one
最右侧的那部电梯是唯一一部
that descends to the sub-basement.
通往地下二层的电梯
You make a right, you go into the control room.
右转 进入控制室
When you're inside...
当你进去后
you fuck yourself.
你自己想办法吧
Tell us how to open it.
告诉我们如何打开它
I don't feel like it.
我不告诉你
Tell us how to open the gate, or we're gonna kill your brother.
告诉我们怎么开门 否则我们杀了你哥哥
Fine.
随便
Kill him.
杀了他
I'm not fucking around.
我没在开玩笑
Yeah, me neither.
我也是
Him out of the way, the seat's all mine.
他死了 至高位就是我的了
Well, that's some cold blooded shit.
真是冷血
So, who abandoned who?
那么 谁抛弃了谁？
Hmm?
嗯？
Back in the day.
当年
Shut up.
闭嘴
You, right?
你 对吗？
You're older.
你是姐姐
She's just been holding you back all day.
她今天一整天都在拖你后腿
You know she's gonna leave you again, right?
你知道她还会再次抛弃你的 对吧？
Shut the fuck up!
闭上你的狗嘴
Fucking hit me!
敢打我
Grace!
格蕾丝
Who?
谁啊
Yes, yes, run her down!
对 对 撞死她
That's my bitch!
这就是我的婊子
Get out of the road!
别被撞死了
What?!
什么？
I think she's leaving, boss.
我想她已经走了 老兄
Fuck!
操
Grace?!
格蕾丝
Faith, Go!
费丝 快跑
What are you doing?
你在干什么？
Get out!
快走
Run!
跑
Give it up, Grace.
放弃吧 格蕾丝
This is for the best.
这是最好的结局
Get the fuck off her!
滚吧你
Come on!
快点
One, two, three, come on!
一 二 三 起来
Okay, alright.
好吧 好吧
Oh my god!
哦天呐
We're gonna get into a golf cart!
我们要上高尔夫球车
Come on!
快点
Let's go. let's go, let's go!
走 走 走
"Kill him."
“杀了他”
"I don't care."
“我不在意”
I was stalling, you idiot.
我是在拖延时间 白痴
I surely did a number on you.
我肯定对你做了不少事
You look at the...
你看...
Stop treating me like I'm a fucking child.
别他妈把我当小孩子
Okay.
好吧
I am ready to take the field.
我准备好上场了
You're not allowed to, actually.
实际上你不被允许上场
You abdicated.
你放弃了
You're no longer the head of your family.
你不再是家族的族长了
And your wife controls all of your assets.
而且你的妻子控制着你所有的资产
Even though she's chosen not to hunt, she still represents your family.
即使她选择不参与狩猎 她仍然代表你的家族
Pardon?
什么
You own nothing.
你一无所有
I think, uh...
我想 呃
I think I need to lie down.
我想我需要躺下
Where shall I send your brother's remains?
你兄弟的遗骸该送到哪里？
To your mother's asshole.
送去你妈的屁眼里
You fuck.
你这混蛋
Have a nice nap.
睡个好觉
Fuck you!
操你
还有你
And fuck you, you creepy little fuck!
还有你 你这变态小杂种
I fucking hate all of you!
我他妈的恨死你们了
Fuck you too.
你也去死吧
Okay.
好吧
That's not at all sad.
你一点都不难过
I'm ready.
我准备好了
Give me the fucking pen.
给我那该死的笔
Come on.
快点
Come on, run, run, run.
快 跑 跑 跑
told you to fucking run.
跟你说了要跑
Just sit.
坐下
Let me...let me help pull it out.
让我帮你拔出来
It's gotta come out!
必须拔出来
I'm gonna find you something for the pain.
我去给你找点止痛的东西
Oh!
哦
There's pepper spray.
要辣椒喷雾吗？
You don't think?
你脑子蠢吗？
You don't listen?
你听不懂人话吗？
Out of all the options in front of you,
所有选项摆在你面前
you always manage to pick the dumbest one.
你偏偏次次都选最蠢的那个
It's actually impressive.
真厉害啊
How do you do it?
你怎么每次都能那么蠢的
I saved you.
我救了你
You could have saved yourself.
你本来可以自救的
You could have gotten help.
你本可以去找救援
I can't take care of both of us.
我照顾不了我们俩
I can't do it.
我真的做不到
Oh, it's all my fault.
哦 都是我的错
And I know. I'm such a burden.
我知道 我真是个累赘
You're a fucking child!
你还真是个孩子
The only reason I'm fucking here is because of you,
我他妈来这里唯一的原因就是你
and now I'm gonna fucking die here because of you!
而现在我他妈要死在这里也是因为你
You would have died hours ago if it wasn't for me.
要不是我 你几小时前就死了
Oh, I'm sorry I didn't run away and abandon you, but that's more your thing.
哦 抱歉我没跑掉把你扔下 但这事儿更像你的作风
I was right to fucking leave.
我离开是对的
And I wish you never goddamn found me.
我真希望你他妈从没找到我
You're right.
你说得对
I should have run.
我应该跑的
Good luck.
祝你好运
And fuck off.
滚吧
Faith, wait!
费丝 等等
Hi, cunt.
嗨 贱人
Bye, cunt.
再见 贱人
Fuck.
操
Really?
真的？
Fuck.
操你妈
All alone again?
又一个人了
Huh?
哈？
Thought you could fuck with me.
以为你能搞我
Where's your sister?
你姐姐呢
She's gone!
她走了
She's probably bringing the cops right now!
她现在正在带警察过来
We own the cops.
我们掌管着警察
Goddammit!
该死
Where the fuck are you, whore?
你他妈在哪儿 婊子？
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ 转身来 ♪
I'm gonna tear you apart!
我要把你撕碎
♪ Every now and then, I get a little bit lonely ♪
♪ 偶尔我会孤单 心头猛地沉甸甸 ♪
♪ And you're never coming 'round ♪
♪ 你却总不会再出现 ♪
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ 转身来 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I get a little bit tired ♪
♪ 偶尔我会疲惫 ♪
♪ Of listening to the sound of my tears ♪
♪ 厌倦听自己哭声回旋 ♪
¡Hija de puta!
（西班牙语）你个臭婊子
♪ Turn around ♪
♪ 转身来 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I get a little bit nervous ♪
♪ 偶尔我会紧张 ♪
♪ That the best of all the years have gone by ♪
♪ 怕光阴里最好的年华溜远 ♪
♪ Turn around... ♪
♪ 转身来... ♪
Slowing your sister down is the only significant
拖累你姐姐 是你这辈子做过的
thing you've ever done and will ever do.
也是你以后唯一能做到的有意义的事
You're not even a person.
你连个人都算不上
It's just a collection of organs and...
只是一堆器官和
meaningless opinions... approximating a person.
加上一堆毫无意义的想法...勉强拼凑成个人形
♪ ...And then I see the look in your eyes ♪
♪ ...但又看见你眼里的光芒 ♪
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ 转身来 睁开眼 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I fall apart ♪
♪ 偶尔我会崩溃 四分五裂 ♪
♪ Turn around, bright eyes ♪
♪ 转身来 睁开眼 ♪
♪ Every now and then, I fall apart ♪
♪ 偶尔我会崩溃 四分五裂 ♪
♪ And I need you now tonight ♪
♪ 我今晚多想你 ♪
♪ And I need you more than ever ♪
♪ 此刻比任何时候都更需要你 ♪
♪ And if you only hold me tight ♪
♪ 只要你紧紧抱我一次 ♪
♪ We'll be holding on forever ♪
♪ 我们就能永远相依 ♪
♪ And we'll only be making it right ♪
♪ 我们会把一切修正成对 ♪
♪ 'Cause we'll never be wrong ♪
♪ 因为我们不会错 ♪
♪ Together, we can take it to the end of the line ♪
♪ 并肩走到尽头的尽头 ♪
♪ Your love is like a shadow on me all of the time ♪
♪ 你的爱像影子缠绕我始终 ♪
♪ I really need you tonight ♪
♪ 我今晚真的需要你 ♪
♪ Forever's gonna start tonight ♪
♪ 永远 就从今晚开始 ♪
I've been dreaming about this moment.
我一直期盼着这一刻
You obviously don't know where you are.
你显然不清楚自己现在在哪
This is my house.
这是我的地盘
And the house always wins.
而庄家永远都赢
How long have you been saving that one for?
这句话你憋多久了？
Fucking douchebag.
他妈的混蛋
This was my mother's dress.
这是我母亲的裙子
All she ever wanted was for me to be happy.
她唯一的心愿就是让我幸福
And Alex made me happy.
而亚历克斯让我幸福
Shut up.
闭嘴
You're fucking crazy.
你疯了
I'm gonna kill you now.
我现在就要杀了你
You stole him.
你偷走了他
You changed him.
你改变了他
Dude, he didn't fucking love you.
姐 他根本不爱你
Titus!
泰特斯
Titus, stop!
泰特斯 停下
Titus, what the fuck are you doing?
泰特斯 你他妈在干什么
I'm killing this girl!
我要杀了这女孩
Jesus Christ, Titus, we don't have time...
天呐 泰特斯 我们没时间陪你...
Titus, wait!
泰特斯 等等
We can use her.
我们可以利用她
Faith!
费丝
Grace, I know you're out there.
格蕾丝 我知道你在外面
I have your sister, Grace.
我抓到了你妹妹 格蕾丝
Don't you worry, she's doing...
别担心 她...
well, she's doing just peachy.
嗯 她还没被揍烂掉
Go on
说话
Grace?
格蕾丝
Yeah.
好啊
If you don't return to the lobby within the next ten minutes, she dies.
如果你在接下来的十分钟内不回到大厅 她就会死
Grace, just leave me.
格蕾丝 别管我
- Grace, just leave me. - After she's dead,
- 格蕾丝 别管我 - 她死后
I'm gonna find you, Grace,
我会找到你 格蕾丝
wherever you are, and I'm gonna kill you.
不管你在哪儿 我都会杀了你
So, if you want to save your sister,
如果你想救你的妹妹
get your ass to the lobby.
滚到大厅来
Hey.
嘿
After I kill your sister...
在我杀了你姐姐后
...you and I are gonna have more fun.
我和你好好玩玩
Take her to the lodge.
把她带去小屋
（安保武器）
Back for round two, bitch!
回来第二轮了 婊子
Yeah.
对
Say hi to Alex for me.
替我向亚历克斯问好
She's fucking here.
她他妈在这里
Oh, Christ!
哦 天呐
Help me, you fucking turd!
帮帮我 你这混蛋
Faith!
费丝
Grace?
格蕾丝
Where's my sister?
我妹妹在哪儿？
I don't know.
我不知道
I'm not playing anymore.
我不玩了
I'm an innocent bystander.
我是个无辜的旁观者
Oh shit, shit, shit!
哦 妈的 妈的 妈的
Fuck!
操
Grace?
格蕾丝
Faith!
费丝
Where is she?
她在哪儿？
I...I don't know.
我不知道
I don't know.
Tell me where she is!
告诉我她在哪儿？
I don't...
我不...
Tell me where she is.
告诉我她在哪儿？
Ah!
啊!
God!
天呐
Ah!
啊!
Let's dance, puta!
让我们起舞吧 婊子
Shit.
妈的
Fuck.
操
Faith, no!
费丝 不
Get out of there, Grace!
快给我出来格蕾丝
Grace!
格蕾丝
Fuck you!
操
That glass may be two inches thick, but I can still
那块玻璃虽然有两英寸厚
blow your sister's brains all over this window.
但我照样能把你妹妹的脑浆喷得满窗都是
Grace!
格蕾丝
You only have three seconds.
你只有三秒钟
- Three... - Don't do it!
- 三... - 别这么做
Two...
二...
Don't listen to him!
别听他的
One...
一...
Okay! Okay!
行 好
Stop! Stop!
停手 停手
I'll come out! I'll come out!
我出来 我出来
No!
不要
Grace!
格蕾丝
Don't!
不要出来
Grace!
格蕾丝
If you marry me... Grace!
如果你嫁给我 格蕾丝...
No!
不要
Look at me!
看着我
I would rather die than you lose your soul!
我宁可死也不愿让你失去灵魂
That woman, she said there's a loophole to all this.
那个女人说 这一切都有漏洞
She said if we get married...
她说 如果我们结婚...
you get your seat...
你就能得到席位...
and I get to live.
而我也能活下去
Don't know if we'll be able to get her out before dawn.
不知道我们能不能在天亮前把她弄出来
Fuck it.
去他的
I accept your proposal.
我接受你的求婚
No!
不
Okay.
好的
Okay, Good.
好
Good.
很好
I'm going to need some assurances first so I know
我得先得到一些保证 这样我才放心
you're not just going to kill us both when I come out.
我出来的时候 你可别把我们俩都杀了
I swear to you... Oh, don't swear to me!
我向你发誓...哦 别向我发誓
Fucking shit for brains!
他妈的白痴
Swear to Mr. LeBail!
向勒贝尔先生发誓
I swear to Mr. LeBail that no harm shall come to you or your sister.
我向勒贝尔先生发誓 不会伤害你或你妹妹
You can't...
你不能
I'm so sorry.
我很抱歉
I'll have everything you need brought in.
我会让人把你需要的一切都拿来
Get ready.
做好准备
The guests are already arriving for coronation.
参加加冕典礼的宾客已经陆续抵达
I thought maybe we could have a toast.
我想我们不妨干杯庆祝一下
We're about to become family.
我们就要成为一家人了
Grace, I never wanted to hurt you.
格蕾丝 我从没想伤害你
But I had to follow the rules.
但是我必须遵守规则
Listen, we don't have a lot of time.
听着 我们时间不多了
So I'm just gonna say it.
所以我就直说了
I'm scared.
我害怕
It's my brother.
我哥哥
I didn't understand...
我不明白
who he really is.
他到底是谁
I spent my whole life...
我花了一辈子
searching for the good in him.
寻找他身上的优点
You know what I found?
你知道我找到了什么
Nothing.
什么都没有
Absolutely fucking nothing.
他妈什么也没有
I thought I could keep him in check.
我以为我能控制住他
But he's lost it.
但他已经失控了
Grace, I need your help.
格蕾丝 我需要你的帮助
We have to try to control him together.
我们必须一起努力控制他
Having a seat doesn't have to be bad.
拥有一个席位不见得就是坏事
Think about all the good we could do with that power.
想想我们能用那种权力做多少好事
But I need you at my side.
但我需要你在我身边
Hey, Grace.
嘿 格蕾丝
You're not like us.
你不像我们
You have hope.
你有希望
I don't now.
我现在没有
You took it from me.
是你夺走了它
We are good at that.
我们很擅长这个
A little girl time.
来点姐妹时间
Thank you for showing me who you really are.
谢谢你让我看清了你的真面目
Titus, it's not a ...
泰特斯 听我解释...
Titus, stop.
泰特斯 停下
You want to control me.
你想控制我
No.
不
You want all the power for yourself.
你想要所有的权力
No.
不
You do.
你想
你就是这么想的
You always do.
你总是这样
Titus stop, please!
泰特斯 停下 求你了
Look at me, Grace.
看着我 格蕾丝
Grace, look at me!
Get her to look at me.
让她看着我
I want you to see this, Grace.
我要你看到这个 格蕾丝
I want you to see this.
我要你看到这个
Grace!
格蕾丝
I want you to see who I am.
我要你看到我是谁
I want you to see that I am not a man who can be controlled.
我要你看清楚 我不是一个可以被人掌控的人
You mentioned the rules.
你提到了规则
There's nothing in the rules about killing a family member.
规则里没有关于杀害家族成员的内容
Try to keep me in check now.
现在来试试控制我啊
Just try it.
试试看
I told you it would be me who got you.
我告诉过你 会是我抓住你
I'll see you at the altar.
我们祭坛见
You can't...do this
你不能...这么做
I have to.
我必须这么做
There's no other way.
没有别的办法
It's okay.
没事的
Shem HaMephorash!
谢姆·汉普拉
I can't see shit move.
我他妈什么都看不见
Nomine satani Lucifer excelsis.
至高无上的撒旦路西法之名
In the name of our great and eternal benefactor,
奉我们伟大而永恒的恩主之名
come forth and bestow your blessing upon these.
请现身 赐福予众人
In the names of Satan, Lucifer, Baliel, Leviathan,
以撒旦 路西法 巴利尔 利维坦之名
come forth and bear witness.
现身并作证
Hail Satan.
撒旦万岁
Hail Satan!
Welcome, everyone.
欢迎 各位
I'm pleased so many of you could make it.
我很高兴有这么多人能来
Not only do we have our coronation this fine morning,
不仅在这个美好的早晨举行加冕仪式
we also have a wedding.
我们还有一场婚礼
Our cup runneth over.
我们的福杯满盈
Titus.
泰特斯
Your hand, please.
请伸出你的手
Your vows being made by intent, by the power of Satan,
既然你们的誓言是出于本意 且受撒旦之力所驱使
I now confer the possession of each other upon you.
我现在宣布你们彼此归属
Titus Chester Danforth.
泰特斯·切斯特·丹福斯
Do you take this woman, in this world and the next?
你愿意娶这位女士 并承诺与她共度今生与来世吗？
Unto the fires of hell?
哪怕是下地狱的烈火？
I do.
我愿意
And do you, Grace Elizabeth MacCaullay Le Domas, take this man to be yours?
而你 格蕾丝·伊丽莎白·麦考利·勒多马斯 愿意接受这个男人
In flesh and spirit, in this world and the next?
在肉体和精神上 并承诺与他共度今生与来世吗？
Unto the fires of hell?
哪怕是下地狱的烈火？
I do.
我愿意
What he hath forged in hell, let no mortal tear asunder.
他在地狱中锻造之物 任凭凡人休想拆解
We ask this in thy name, O Lord.
主啊 我们奉你的名祈求
I now pronounce you man and wife.
我现在宣布你们结为夫妻
You may kiss the bride.
你可以亲吻新娘了
Titus Danforth, is hereby granted the high seat of the council of Libecia.
泰特斯·丹福斯 特此授予利贝西亚议会至高席位
Hail Satan.
撒旦万岁
Hail Satan!
- Hail Satan! - Hail Satan!
- 撒旦万岁 - 撒旦万岁
What the fuck?
搞什么
It's not against the rules to kill a family member.
杀死自己的家族成员不违反规则
Thank you for that.
感谢你的提醒
It's me who got you.
是我抓住了你
the fuck is happening?
他妈发生了什么
Get on your knees!
跪下
Shem HaMephorash.
舍姆·哈姆·法拉什
This means I can do whatever I want, right?
这意味着我可以为所欲为 对吧
That is correct.
对的
I could lead this organization.
我可以领导这个组织
I could change the world.
我可以改变世界
So as my first act as the head of your high council
因此 作为我担任最高委员会主席后的第一项举措
I hereby remove myself
我特此宣布将我自己
from the council and this entire fucking organization!
从这个委员会 以及这整个他妈的组织中移除
Bro, can she even do that?
兄弟 她可以那样做吗
There's surprisingly little language about this in the bylaws,
出人意料的是 章程对此几乎只字未提
since no one believed anyone would ever willingly give away so much power.
因为没有人相信会有人愿意主动放弃如此大的权力
Okay, but then who gets the fucking seat?
好吧 但然后谁得到那个该死的席位
Whoever's wearing the ring by dawn.
黎明前谁戴着戒指就是谁
When's dawn?
黎明什么时候
In three minutes, give or take.
大约三分钟后
But it's just the council families or...
但只有议会家族还是
Literally anyone.
严格来说任何人
And you said if no one's wearing the ring by dawn, Mr. LeBail would be...
而你说如果黎明前没人戴戒指 勒贝尔先生会
Very upset.
非常不高兴
Choke on it, you inbred fucks!
去吃屎吧 你们这些近亲繁殖的混蛋
I'm coming, my lord!
我来了 我的真神
Shem HaMephorash!
舍姆·哈姆·法拉什
Hail Satan!
撒旦万岁
Fuck, fuck, fuck, fuck!
操 操 操 操
Oh, wow!
哦 哇
I'll kill you.
我会杀了你的
Fucking...
操...
Someone had to burn it all down.
总得有人把这一切付之一炬
You are good at destroying things.
你很擅长毁掉一切
You're free.
你自由了
See ya.
再见
Bye.
拜
Hi, yeah.
你好呀
Hey, yeah, don't look there.
嘿 对 别看那里
Oops
哎哟
Fuck yeah!
操 太爽了
I'm alive, bitches!
我还活着 婊子们
We made it!
我们还活着
Holy fucking shit!
我了个大草
I've renounced my pack, so I've been spared too!
我已经脱离了组织 所以才幸免于难
Let's fucking party!
让我们他妈的开派对
Jesus Christ!
天呐
What's that?
那是谁？
Meow.
咩
Can we go?
我们能走了吗
Meow.
咩
Okay.
好的
Rocket launcher.
叫你玩火箭筒
Come on, let's go!
来 我们走
I love you.
我爱你
I love you too.
我也爱你
I missed you.
我想你了
Yeah, well, you know, I'm not gonna have to anymore.
是啊 不过你知道 以后我不必再这么想了
You're gonna get really fucking sick of me.
你会他妈烦死我的
Promise?
保证？
I do.
我保证
What are you gonna do with the goat?
你打算怎么处理那只山羊？
I don't know.
我不知道
How many times are you gonna get married this week?
你这周打算结几次婚？
It's too soon.
太快了
It's gotta be a record.
肯定破纪录了
Oh.
哦
We're gonna go to the hospital.
我们要去医院
I need a bath.
我要去洗个澡
I stink too.
我也感觉快臭了
字幕贡献者
初稿翻译：pubuqi（SubHD）
二次校对与听译：Borcolasky（SubHD）
终稿校对 听译复核与时间轴：小p（蒙太奇字幕组）